The candy...
It's filling up...
Kobato's wish has changed.
But the contract can't change.
She'll go to the place that she wanted to.
This isn't a gift, it's a curse!
What's happening?
There's somewhere I must go.
Farewell.
What shall I do?
Even the obvious things are always so hard
I just want to grin when I'm happy, sing when I'm in love
They say my dreams will come true someday
but when will someday come? I can't wait!
Count one, two, three and spread my arms
Gather the light to myself
Where is it? Tell me what I can do
Even if I'm hurt so much, even if I run so hard
Even if I collapse crying over and over, I still
believe in my amazing future
Tomorrow...
Are you okay?
Sorry.
Mama wanted us to move this mattress.
A mattress?
Why was there a mattress in an empty room?
Oh!
Fujimoto's helping us move it.
Has your arm healed, Kiyokazu?
Yeah. They just want me to take it easy for another month.
Oh. Thanks.
What are those, Mama?
I thought I'd try to find a new tenant.
That room's been empty since even before you moved in, Kiyokazu.
There should be someone in there to take care of it.
Oh, right.
Chitose...
I go in and air it out every once in a while,
so why don't we leave it empty a little longer?
Why?
Huh?
Sorry, forget I said anything.
Haven't seen you in a while, Kiyokazu.
Have you really been skipping lectures?
Yeah.
I thought you wanted to be a lawyer.
They said you haven't even been taking notes when you do show up.
What's wrong?
Nothing in particular.
Something's up with you.
Something took the wind out of your sails.
Not really.
I guess it's understandable. You did lose something important to you.
It's been, what, three months now?
It's really too bad what happened to the nursery.
I'm not really worried about that. Just...
Just...?
Nah...
Never mind.
Thank you.
The kids were thinking about Yomogi.
So we all came to see it!
Fujimoto, I...
Lately I've been thinking about starting Yomogi Nursery back up.
Okiura says that this time he'll be behind me 100%.
That's great.
Thanks. You take care too, okay?
Okay?
I'm worried about how down you've seemed at school.
Domoto, you-
Once we get everything started back up, why don't you come on a field trip with us?
That's a great idea. We'll get everyone-
Everyone?
Yeah, a field trip with everyone.
Wow, a field trip!
Yes.
Where are we going!?
I want to go too!
Of course. Let's all go together.
Right, Fujimoto?
Yeah...
Everyone together!
Fujimoto!
You meanie!
I'm sorry!
I'll try my best!
What is this!?
What's going on!?
Why?
Why doesn't anyone remember her!?
Hey!
Good morning.
You're not here about newspaper delivery again, are you.
Yes, I remember.
I can't find anyone who remembers her.
Why can you?
Is that what you want to ask? Is there anything else?
Tell me.
When she disappeared, she said there was somewhere she must go.
What's that supposed to mean?
If you want to hear the truth, you have to promise me
that you won't be too shocked by what I tell you.
Okay?
Yeah.
Long ago, she lost her life due to something unfortunate that occurred in another world.
Her life?
Kobato's wish...
It was to transcend time, and be reborn by the side of her love.
That's what she wished for.
And in order for that wish to be granted,
she was given a task and sent down to earth.
Her soul had only the span of four seasons...
Then, she's already... there?
I don't know.
Over my long, long years with Shuichiro, we've parted in tears so many times.
Shuichiro... The doctor, right?
Yes.
As Shuichiro is reborn...
Yes. As he is reborn, we meet again.
Our hearts are drawn together.
Even if our memories of previous lives are lost...
We still bear the same souls.
As long as our souls continue to pass on, no matter how many times...
I'm sure we'll meet.
I don't know what I would have done if the machinery at the plant had been foreclosed on.
I can't thank you enough, Fukita.
I'm glad it worked out. Let's keep it up.
Thanks.
Oh, Fujimoto.
Yes?
Why don't you take a look at the file on my desk sometime?
I'll be out of the office, so I'd like you to handle it.
Of course.
It's an inheritance case.
Who's that?
Oh, you haven't met him yet?
He's been at my firm for four years now.
Fukita and Associates.
He's young, but he works hard.
Fujimoto! It's from Secretary Hattori at the court.
Okay!
He was a client of mine who passed recently.
His son and daughter-in-law had already passed away,
so in his will of two years ago he specified his granddaughter as the sole heir.
However, the land is from an old estate, so the exact borders are uncertain.
Understood. I'll go check it out in person tomorrow.
Under the summer sky
Within my heart
Oh, so you're the lawyer.
Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to... meet... you.
Even if our memories of previous lives are lost...
Wait!
Stop! Please!
Fujimoto...
You're the person I care the most about.
I always have.
And I always will.
Always...
The piano...
You're good at playing the piano.
Sorry for not asking first.
That's funny, for some reason I feel like I know that melody.
Really? It's a song an old love used to sing.
I've been looking for her for a long time.
Oh? I hope you find her.
Yeah.
Anyway, do you mind if I inspect the house?
Go right ahead.
Everything checks out.
I just have to go back to the office and clear up the formalities.
Sure! Thank you.
And... I have to give this back to you.
Er?
Candy?
Can you sing that song for me one more time?
Of course!
The flowers which bloom in spring, the wide summer sky
Within my heart their shine remains
Even on days I close my windows to shut out the morning rain
Fluttering within my heart, the light breaks through the clouds
Are you okay?
So that was it...
The place I wanted to go...
The person I wanted to be with...
I thought if I had just one more chance, this time we could be happy together.
I was so silly.
Kobato?
I'm back!
You've kept me waiting so many years.
You're late again.
Fujimoto!
Joy and sadness, I embrace them both and keep going
My hand and yours join together strongly
On the shore in the autumn, in winter, sleeping in the treetops
The endless kindness of this world
As night falls, let us offer our prayers
That's all there is to it.
That idiot decides that even after finishing his task he's going to keep protecting her.
So he's staying in the human world, and we're stuck making baumkuchen.
And silently welcome tomorrow's sun
Yeah.
At least baumkuchen's tasty.
There we go. 100 points for me.
A faraway voice leads me on
Like it's smiling, like it's singing, the echoing sound of the wind
Joy and sadness, I embrace them both and keep going
My hand and yours join together strongly